Mr. Faulk? James Sandin.
Hey, Mr. Sandin.
I talked to John over at
repairs, and he took care of it.
It's all fine.
The system is working
without a hitch.
You are going to be
locked in tight tonight.
Thank you, sir.
All right, Mr. Faulk.
Safe night.
James Sandin's office.
Sue? Yeah,
I took care of Faulk.
What do you know,
did you hear anything?
You're number one, Mr. Sandin.
You got it, sir.You came out on top/
All right. Yeah
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Congratulations
to you, too, Susan.
You don't have to say that.
No, Susan, it's a team win/
Thank you.
Okay. All right,
well, safe night.
Safe night, Mr. Sandin.
The poor can't afford to protect
themselves.
They're the victims tonight.
We all got our own opinions.
That's what makes this country great.
Holly, line four.
What are your Purge plans?
Locking down behind my
brand new security system.
Pete from Northern Virginia,
what's your Purge plan?
I'm gonna hunt down my boss.
That son of a bitch has it coming.
Clearly, more people will be Purging
this year than ever before.
American streets will
be running red tonight,
when people release the beast
in record numbers.
Mr. Cali! You're getting one
last walk in before lockdown, huh?
Yup.
Did you do the systems
check I recommended?
Of course. No problems.
Yeah, it's the same one I use.
I only sell the best.
Nobody's bothering us tonight.
You have a safe night, Mr. Sandin.
Thanks.
Don't forget to buy your blue Baptisias.
Display those flowers
proudly, folks, okay?
Show your support
for this important evening.
Safe night to everyone.
Home again, home again.
Jiggity-jig.
Release the beast,
and Purge in our American streets.
Your New Founding Fathers...
Hey, honey, I'm home!
I'm in the kitchen.
What a day, what a day.
Everybody's doing security
checks, it's crazy.
Traffic's even worse
than last year.
Something smells good.
Hey.
Ta-da!/ Ah.
I'll put them in water,
get them outside.
Okay. Where are the kids?
Their rooms, of course.
We got an hour
before commencement, right?
Mmm-hmm. Dinner's nearly ready,
so, uh, hurry up/
All right.
Well, I have to make a few phone calls/
Mmm-hmm.
Oh.
One thing? Yeah?
Zoey is getting worse.
She's been pouting all day.
I can't stand it.
So, you're gonna have to do something
about the Henry situation.
There's nothing to do about it.
He's 18, he's not
getting any younger.
She's just gonna have to sulk.
She'll get over it.
But I've got some good
news for all of us.
I'll tell you at dinner.
History has proven this over
and over again.
We are inherently
a violent species.
Wars, genocide, murder.
The denial of our true
selves is the problem.
The Purge not only contains societal
violence to a single evening,
but the country-wide catharsis
creates psychological stability
by letting us release the aggression
we all have inside of us.
I love you.
Let's growl.
What?
Growl. Why?
Because everyone says,
"I love you."
It's used, and we need
to find our own thing.
Go like this...
No, I'll look silly.
Come on/
No.
Do it. It's our way of saying,
"I love you." Try it.
Do it.
I think my dad's home.
I'm sorry, baby. You've
got to get going.
I'm sorry.
And you have to get
home before lockdown.
Come on.
Come here.
Someone's getting
ready for tonight.
Be careful.
Mary!
I'm so glad I caught you.
I come bearing gifts.
What have I done
to deserve a gift, Grace?
Oh, I have a new hobby.
Baking/ Grace. Mary.
I made way too many cookies.
Hi!/
Ooh! Cookies!
I hope you're hungry...
Those cookies are crazy good.
They're lovely.
Have a safe night, ladies.
Bye! Good night!
Bye! Thank you, Grace.
Yeah, just what the Halversons needed.
More cookies, right?
Oh!
The new addition you built,
it's just amazing.
Thank you.
You know, not everyone had the
year you did, Mary.
What d'you mean?
You know your husband
sold a new security system
to almost every home
in this community.
You know, some people
are actually saying...
this neighborhood paid for that
new addition on your home.
Are people really saying that?
Relax, it's just good old
neighborhood gossip.
Nothing to worry about.
You're too sensitive.
So, are you having your
annual party, Grace?
No. Too much trouble.
We're just gonna lock down,
watch some Purge events.
Nothing special.
Well, um,
thank you for the cookies.
Good night.
You're welcome.
Have a safe night, Mary.
And you, Grace.
Christ.
You scared me to death.
You can't keep creeping up
on me like that, Charlie.
So, quit playing with Timmy and come
help me set the table, kiddo. Okay?
Now.
Christ! Charlie,
that's twice today.
You're gonna give me
a heart attack.
Sorry, Mom.
Look, check it out. I made
some adjustments to Timmy.
I installed
a night vision program
and I insulated his motor,
so you can barely hear him.
And he can now play music to
accompany him on his missions.
See?
He likes songs from olden times/
Mmm-hmm.
That is very, very cool.
What is it?
What's bothering you?
It's tonight, isn't it?
Just remember all the good
the Purge does, okay?
It's all that matters.
Are you hungry?
A little bit.
Good.
Okay look, take Timmy away and come
back and help me finish up, okay?
Mmm. Okay.
Honey, this food is so good.
Isn't it amazing? Not one carb.
Oh, great/
Not one.
Well, I'd like to hear
about everybody's day.
Zoey, you want to go first?
Charlie, what are you doing?
Sorry, I forgot
to take my vitals earlier.
Honey...
By the way, there's a slight
deviation in my heart rate,
but other than that,
nothing to worry about.
Okay, thank you.
Zoey, your day.
I don't want to do this anymore.
It's stupid.
Okay, fine.
Calc test, piano. Normal day/
Mmm-hmm.
Who cares?
I do. I care, very much.
And what about practice?
You ready for your recital?
James.
Of course you are,
because you're always ready.
Just make sure your left hand
cooperates in that third movement.
When I'm listening,
that's what I hear.
All right, can I...
Does anybody mind?
Can I do my day?
I have some news/ Go ahead/
Um...
I did it. I did it.
All sales are final...
And I'm on top.
My division sold the most
upgraded security systems.
Congratulations, Dad/
Thank you.
Congratulations, baby.
Thanks. It's a team
effort, you know?
All right, Charlie,
you're next.
Well, we studied the history
of tonight in History.
And in English, I wrote a story
about a man whose love is so
powerful, that it can kill people.
So, he cuts out his own heart.
That is so sweet.
You know, he should have
cut off his own penis.
Zoey, Zoey...
Eating dinner, no penises!
Charlie, don't encourage her.
Don't fist-bump that!
We're not
in the dormitorium, okay?
"Dormitorium?"
Is that even a word?
Get with the times. God.
Guys, look what time it is.
Oh, wow, it's later than I thought.
All right, it's time
for lockdown. Let's go.
Don't even think about it.
Hey, give that back/
Are we in the zoo?
Fine, I want this.
Hey, look at this.
Mr. Sabian and Mr. Barbero
are going hunting.
That's daring.
I didn't know they were
going to Purge together.
Are they friends?
Hmm. The Ferrins
are having a party.
Grace said she wasn't
having a party this year.
Just thank God
we weren't invited.
She's nice. But, wow,
she's annoying.
All right, let's get
ready for tonight.
As always, just a precaution.
All right, Mr. Cali is
starting his lockdown.
Okay.
We ready?
All right, let's hit it.
Okay, Charlie, it's
almost time. Hit it.
Release the beast
and Purge in our American streets.
Your New Founding Fathers
encourage your participation.
This is not a test.
This is your
Emergency Broadcast System
announcing the commencement
of the Annual Purge
sanctioned by
the U. S. Government.
Weapons of Class Four and lower
have been authorized
for use during the Purge.
All other weapons
are restricted.
Government officials
of ranking 10
have been granted
immunity from the Purge
and shall not be harmed.
Commencing at the siren,
any and all crime,
including murder,
will be legal for
12 continuous hours.
Police, fire and emergency medical
services will be unavailable
until tomorrow morning at 7:00
AM when the Purge concludes.
Blessed be our
New Founding Fathers
and America, a nation reborn.
May God be with you all.
Okay, kids. Now, I know bad
things do happen tonight.
But we can afford protection.
So, we'll be fine, just like always.
No worries.
Okay? Okay ?
Can I go now?
I would prefer to be
miserable in my room.
Of course you may.
Thank you for being here.
Charlie.../
Where are you going, bud?
Hey/
Charlie.
Why don't you guys do it?
Because we don't feel the
need to, Charlie. That's all.
So, if you felt the need to,
you would kill someone tonight?
Look, I know this is difficult
to understand at your age,
but tonight allows
people a release
for all the hatred and
violence and aggression
that they keep up inside them.
Okay? And yes,
if your mother and I were so
inclined, uh, we would participate.
Because it works.
You don't remember
how bad it was, Charlie.
The poverty, all the crime.
This night saved our country.
Hey...
Why don't you go relax?
We're all done here.
I've got some paperwork
to process to get my bonus.
Then we should watch a
movie later with the kids.
Jesus, Henry!
You scared the hell out of me.
Wait, what are you doing here?
I wanted to surprise you.
So, I snuck in
when you were eating.
Baby, you can't be in here.
My dad will lose his mind
if he sees you here now.
Come on.
Aren't you happy to see me?
Of course.
We're looking at some
live feeds from around the country
and discussing the Purge with
criminologist Tommy Aagaard.
Thanks, Nicole.
Now, is the Purge really
about releasing aggression
and containing violence,
or is it something else?
Purge detractors
often postulate
this evening is actually about
the elimination of the poor,
the needy, the sick.
Those unable
to defend themselves.
The eradication
of the so-called
"non-contributing members"
of society,
ultimately unburdening
the economy.
Is the Purge
really about money?
Either way, crime is down.
The economy is flourishing.
I can't do this.
Um...
Did I do something?/
No. I... Um...
I just...
I didn't come here to see you.
I came to see your father.
What? Why?
It's time to straighten this out.
He cannot forbid you
from seeing me.
That's crazy.
It might be crazy, but he's
not going to change his mind.
He thinks
you're too old for me.
Talking to him is only going
to make him more angry
and he'll make it
more difficult for us.
I promise everything
is gonna be okay.
America was collapsing.
A quadruple dip recession
followed by a full market crash.
A skyrocketing debt,
multiple wars
and a significant
dollar devaluation...
All precipitating
the worst economic disaster
in the history
of the United States.
Crime and poverty
rose exponentially,
and the New Founding Fathers,
just months after being elected
came up with
this audacious notion,
the decriminalization
of murder for one night.
A lawful outlet
for American rage.
A way to contain crime.
The undeniable fact is,
this is working.
I thought I heard gunshots.
A couple of streets back,
maybe?
Gunshots aren't gonna happen tonight, okay?
It's nothing.
It's probably somebody just
firing off a few rounds
before going hunting.
Come on. Let's go relax.
Hold on.
Look. He can't kick me out.
He's gonna be forced to
listen to what I have to say.
I don't know.
One on one. Man to man, no BS.
I'm gonna explain to him
that sure, I may be older,
but you're also very mature.
So age difference
is not a problem.
I'll tell him
how much I love you.
10 years ago,
we could barely afford rent.
Now we're thinking about buying a boat.
Crazy.
Yeah... Uh-oh.
This one has a car garage.
Who needs a car on a boat?
They're coming after me.
They're gonna kill me!
Can anyone hear me?
Help me!
Someone, please, help me!
They're coming
after me, all right?
Can anybody help me?
Please. They killed...
I just need to get
somewhere safe.
Does anybody hear me?
Look, I won't hurt you!
I don't want to die.
I don't deserve this.
Why won't anybody help me?
I just need somewhere to hide.
Somebody, please, just
open the door for me.
They're coming, they're coming.
Somebody, please!
They're gonna kill me!
What the hell?
Come here!
Let's go! This way!
Come on!
Hurry!
Come on! Hurry!
What the hell?
Charlie! Zoey!
This way! Hurry!
Go! Go!
Hurry!
What the hell is going on?
Mr. Sandin.
James, he has a gun!
Henry has a gun!
Oh, my God!
Henry!
Henry! Henry!
Oh, God!
James. Are you hit?
I didn't hit Zoey, did I?
I think she's okay.
Zoey! Zoey!
Charlie, come here.
Mom, what's going on?
Charlie, where is he, huh?
Where's the man?
I don't know.
I don't understand.
Who is he? Why did you
let him in our home?
He was hurt. He called for help.
No one was helping him.
Charlie, Jesus Christ.
What the hell? Huh?
We have no idea what
this man is capable of.
Enough. Enough, James.
He's gone. We don't know
what Henry might do.
And we're not safe out here.
We don't know where Zoey is.
You're right.
Let's go. Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
Henry! Henry.
Hang on.
Henry!
Come on.
Henry?
Okay...
Here's the plan.
You two stay put here,
and I'll just...
I'll go out there
and I'm gonna find Zoey
and I'm gonna
bring her back here.
Henry tried to kill you.
James...
I know. Mary, I got
to make sure she's okay.
Okay? I have to.
He didn't shoot at me.
I'll find her,
I can go. I'll be fine.
No, no, no...
I can't let you go
with that man out there.
Okay? I can't let you do that.
Baby, I...
Let me go get her.
You just stay here
with Charlie. Okay?
You be careful, okay?
I will.
Zoey? Zoey?
Zoey? It's me.
You okay, sweetheart?
Yeah, Mom.
Okay.
Mom?
Charlie? Mom?
Charlie, you wait here. I'm gonna
be right outside the door.
Okay.
Zoey.
Zoey?
Mom?
Zoey, sweetheart.
Are you okay? Is Charlie okay?
Where's Dad? Is he all right?/
Everyone's fine.
Mom, I didn't know Henry
was going to do that.
I didn't know he was going to...
Why would he do that?
Mom?/ Charlie, just give
me a second, okay?
Mom, he died/
Keep the door closed.
He's dead. Henry's dead/
Mom?
Mom!
Charlie, just give me a second.
Zoey, let's see
what Charlie wants.
Mom, now!
What is it, baby?
You need to see this.
Tell Dad I'm sorry.
Zoey, please!
Zoey!
Zoey?
Zoey.
Hey, Mr. Sandin,
are you home?
Wait, James,
I have to talk to you.
Henry is dead.
I killed him.
I know. I saw Zoey.
Is she okay? Is she hurt?
Is she in there?
She's not hurt.
I couldn't get her
to come with me.
What are we gonna do?
I have to show you something.
Oh, God, I know.
That one is saying something.
Hey, Mrs. Sandin.
Your home tells me you're
good folk, just like us.
One of the "haves."
And your blue flowers tell me
that you support the Purge.
We want to treat you fairly,
so listen closely.
Let me introduce us.
We are some fine, young,
very educated guys and gals.
We have gotten gussied up
in our most terrifying guises,
as we do every year,
ready to violate, annihilate,
and cleanse our souls.
But things took a turn.
Our target escaped us, and...
Several of your dear neighbors
informed us that you, the Sandins,
have inexplicably
given him sanctuary.
Mr. and Mrs., the man
you're sheltering is nothing
but a dirty, homeless pig.
A grotesque menace
to our just society,
who had the audacity
to fight back,
killing one of us when we
attempted to execute him tonight.
The pig doesn't know his place,
and now he needs
to be taught a lesson.
You need to return him to us.
Alive.
So that we may Purge
as we are entitled.
Here's the plan, Sandins.
You have until our
provisions arrive,
provisions which will help us
break into your elegant home.
If you don't...
If you don't deliver him
by the aforementioned time,
we'll release
the beast on him...
And on you.
And, um, we can enter
any home we want.
And we will want as wanting is
our will on this fine night.
Don't force us to hurt you.
We don't want to kill our own.
Please, just let us Purge.
Toodle-oo, Sandins.
Cut it. Cut it now.
The monitors are
working on backup.
The power's out
in the whole house.
ames, they can't get in here, right?
They can't get into our home.
I don't know.
It's hard to say.
You don't know?
You sell these
security systems.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
We have tested the system. It
works 99 percent of the time.
It looks good. It's strong.
People stay away.
It looks good?
It's not built
for worst-case scenarios.
Is it impenetrable?
No, nothing's impenetrable.
Things like this are not supposed
to happen in our neighborhood.
Well, they are
happening, James.
They're happening right now.
Do you see this?
Okay, listen, just sit down.
Sit down, please.
We gotta calm down. Sit down.
All right. Sit down, sit down.
Listen.
Okay, to answer your question,
yes, they could get in here.
They could tunnel
underneath us.
They could smoke us out.
They could devise
a battering ram, okay?
I'm sorry, but it's true. So,
here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna give
them what they want.
We're gonna find that man and
we're gonna force him outside.
Now, we have guns,
and he doesn't.
But they'll kill him.
Why should he die?
It's him or us, Charlie.
Why don't you
give us the homeless man?
No one will miss him when he's gone.
Pretty please.
Wait...
Shit.
Where is he?
There he is.
Look at me.
Come on, look over here.
Where are you?
Come on.
Dear Mr. Sandin!
Sorry to interrupt, but
I'd love to have a word.
Meet me by your front door. I
just need a moment, good sir.
There you are.
Thank you for accepting
my invitation.
Tell me, why haven't you delivered
the filthy swine to me yet?
Are you protecting him?
I surely hope not, Mr. Sandin.
No. Of course not.
We just can't find him.
You see,
this is a misunderstanding.
My son let him in.
He's a young boy.
He doesn't know better.
But I support what occurs here
tonight 100 percent, okay?
I sell security equipment.
So, I would never deny yours,
or anybody else's
right to Purge.
Just give us the
homeless pig, you fuck!
Sorry about that.
I don't condone
that kind of behavior.
But just keep in mind,
Mr. Sandin...
He was my friend,
and you are not.
Our equipment is arriving soon.
And we will get in.
Send out he, or that...
Will be thee.
I'll go get him.
You should do that.
Hey, Charlie.
I don't know what's going on.
There are people outside.
Um...
And Henry's dead.
I'll be okay. I have his gun.
Stay where you are.
Please be safe, okay?
I'm going to go hide
in your secret spot.
No.
All right? I love you.
Don't.
Zoey.
Get back.
Into the hall. Let's go.
Drop your gun.
Dad, please.
Drop it.
Don't hurt her.
Lower your weapon.
Zoey, I will not
let him hurt you.
Leave her alone,
you son of a bitch.
I will let her go
when this night is over.
You're gonna get us
all killed. You know that.
They're coming in here, and
they are gonna kill us all.
They are gonna come in here,
and they are... Back up.
You got to leave my
family out of this. Okay?
If you don't drop your gun,
I will hurt her
and I will hurt you.
We didn't do anything to you.
We don't deserve this/
I don't deserve this either.
Now, listen, I don't
want to hurt any of you,
but I am not dying tonight!
Drop your gun.
Please/
Drop it.
Put the gun down.
Listen to me. Okay.
You are going to die tonight.
And you can either
die like a man,
and walk outside
there by yourself,
or you can die like a coward
and get my wife and my children
killed along with you.
Okay? So take that gun away
from my daughter's head!
Shoot him, Mary! Shoot him!
Get off me!
Stop!
Shit. Shit.
Mary? Mary!
Zoey!
She's unconscious. She hit her head.
Mary, are you okay?
We got to get some rope/
What?
Mary, we have to get some rope
and we have to tie him up
and get him outside.
And we're gonna end
this goddamn night.
All right? Do you hear me?
Okay. Okay.
All right. Come on,
Charlie, help me.
Sweetheart?
Okay, I'm almost done here. As
soon as you get the legs secure...
You got it? All right, let me see.
Let me see. Alright, good job.
You're doing great, honey.
Here's what we're gonna do. We're
gonna roll him into that chair,
and we're gonna
drag him outside
be done, all right?
Mmm-hmm/ You got it?/
All right, we ready?
Charlie, just concentrate
on your sister, okay?
See if she's waking up.
Except, Charlie,
I need the light.
Thank you, son. All right, okay.
Hey, good job.
You're doing great.
All right. Let me get
the chair, here.
Okay, we are almost done.
I'm gonna pick him up on the
count of three, all right?
You're gonna help me.
Keep the light on us, Charlie.
Ready? One, two...
Three!
Okay.
Great. Now, let's get the
tape and tape him in there.
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey!
I've got him, I've got him.
I got him.
All right. Okay. Okay, all right!
You got to calm down. He's
gonna break this tape!
Press on his wound. What?
Get the letter opener
and press on his wound!
Get the letter
opener on the desk!
All right, grab the letter opener!
No, Mom!
Listen to me. I am just
trying to protect my family.
Just calm down.
Mom!
Come on, do it.
Do it, Mary! Do it!
Press on his wound!
Yes!
Mom!
What? You want her to do it again?
Mom, stop!
Just do it again, Mary.
Okay. All right.
Okay. Ready to sit
in the chair?
Yeah, he's ready. Okay.
Help me up. Help me up.
Ready? Okay.
Stay there, all right? Stop it.
Just let me take you
in this chair. All right?
Mary, where's the tape?
You are making this much more
difficult than it needs to be.
You understand me? Huh?
Christ, look at us.
Look at this man.
Look at what
we're doing to him.
Come on, Mary.
Let's get this over with.
It's okay, Mary.
I can't/
Oh, yes, you can, baby.
Baby, I need you right now, okay?
Hey, look at me. Huh?
Look at me, Mary.
Mary.
It's wrong. It's so wrong/
We don't have a choice.
This is so wrong.
We don't have any other choice.
Don't touch me. Look at you.
No, no, no. Don't touch me.
When did this happen?
James, look at you.
What the hell
happened to us, James?
Charlie.
Charlie? Baby, where did you go?
Charlie?
Charlie!
Charlie, where are you, baby?
Zoey. Hey, are you all right?
Sit down, sit down.
You hit your head.
Are you okay?
Oh, God.
I am so sorry
about Henry, okay?
I'm so sorry.
But we're gonna make it
through tonight, all right?
We will, and everything
is gonna be okay.
It's not gonna be okay.
What?
Look at what you're doing.
Nothing is ever
going to be okay again.
Don't say that.
Save your children.
Take me outside.
Charlie? Charlie!
I want all these barricades down!
Get chains on every
door and every window!
James, where's Zoey?
I don't know, she ran out here.
Those freaks outside
are coming in!
They have chains on the
doors and windows.
They're gonna pull them
off and come inside.
Maybe you were right.
No, I wasn't right
about anything.
You're not sending him outside?
I have another idea.
What are you gonna do?
Charlie!
Charlie, listen to me.
You take this gun, all right.
Dad, are you
sending him outside?
No. All right?
You're gonna go hide
in the basement
and you're not gonna come
out for anybody, all right?
Okay. You're a good boy.
All right, go, go.
You just gave our son a gun.
You want to tell me
what the hell we're doing?
We're gonna fight.
I want you to take this one as well.
Safety's off.
You're gonna use
a lot of rounds.
What do I do?
You're gonna cover the
other side of the house.
This is our home.
Our kids live here.
Anybody tries to come
in, you blast them.
You will not hesitate. Mmm.
Dear Mr. and Mrs.!
I'm sorry to tell you this, but
your time is essentially up.
And you failed!
You failed to deliver
the homeless swine!
I'm very disappointed as you
fine folk should know better!
That piece of filth
that you are protecting
exists only to serve
our need to Purge!
So, I bid thee farewell, sweet Sandins.
Release the beast, boys.
Let the killing commence!
Run!
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Are you hurt?/
No, I'm okay.
We've got to get out of here.
Come on, come on, come on.
Cooper, come look at little lady Sandin.
She's exquisite.
Save her for me.
Dad.
Are you okay?/
Yes, Dad, I'm okay.
You stay here, okay?
Are Mommy and Zoey okay?
Yeah, they're gonna be fine.
Mmm...
Shit.
Shit!
It's okay.
Your soul has been
cleansed, Mr. Sandin.
You've Purged.
Just one question for you.
Was his life
really worth yours?
Your family's?
Thank you for this unforgettable
Purge, Mr. Sandin.
No! No! No!
Get off! Get off of me!
James!
Let go of me! Please, don't!
Please don't kill me.
Please don't!
James!
Please, don't! Please, don't!
Please!
James!
Please! Please, don't!
Don't! Please don't!
James.
Charlie! Charlie!
Zoey!
Dad!
Sorry.
Thank you for your sacrifice.
You got a lot of heart, Mr. Sandin.
Blessed be America...
A nation reborn.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
We saw that you were
having some trouble.
We decided to help you.
You saved us.
I don't know what to say.
Don't thank us too much, Mary.
The truth is, you're ours, not theirs.
What do you mean "ours"?
What do you mean?
Dad?
No, no, no! Dad!
Wait! Wait!
Dad!
James is dead.
Mary and the kids
will have to do.
Let's tie them up. We'll
kill them right here.
No, no, no. What do you mean?
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Come on. No! No!
No!
No! No! No!
Mom! Mom!
Cali, get the tape!
Don't touch
my fucking children!
Don't you touch
my fucking kids!
Let them go! Let them go!
Right now! You let
my fucking kids go!
Shut up, Mary! Shut up!
Right now!
Mary! Shut up!
I swear to God, I will
shoot him right now.
Do you hear me?
Why are you doing this?
Why are you doing
this right now?
When your barricades came down,
we saw an opportunity to cleanse
ourselves of our hatred.
You made so much
money off of us
and then you just
stuck it in our faces.
You all think
you're so damn perfect.
I just need you
to listen to me, Grace.
I'm really begging
you right now.
Do not do this to
my children, please.
They're my children, please.
Please, not my children.
I can't let you do that.
We have to, Mary. That's what
this night is all about.
I am begging you.
I'm really begging you.
I can't let you do this.
We'll be better people and you'll
have sacrificed yourselves
to make the world
a better place.
Mom...
Mom!
You're frightening them.
Please don't.
Please let me hold my children.
Mary, no, no. It's over.
Untie them. It's over.
Please untie my hands. Hmm?
Grace?
It's time for you
to quiet down, Mary,
and let us do
our duty as Americans.
Mom.
Sweetheart...
Zoey, look at me, okay?
Just look at your mama.
Just look at me.
"Blessed be
the New Founding Fathers
for letting us Purge
and cleanse our souls."
"Blessed be America...
Blessed be America,
a nation reborn."
I'll go first and then...
We'll take turns.
Timmy?
Don't move.
Drop your weapons right now.
Untie them, let's go.
Right now.
Your call.
Just get it over with.
Kill us quickly.
No.
Oh, for God's sake! Just do it!
Come on!
Mom, they were going to kill us.
It doesn't matter.
We are gonna play the rest of this
night out in motherfucking peace.
Does anyone have
a problem with that?
Did you enjoy
Grace's Purge party...
Mr. Halverson?
Go fuck yourself.
Sorry, I can't hear you.
It was very nice.
Oh, good.
I'm glad you all
had a grand time.
Didn't you hear what I said?
No more killing tonight!
Is it that hard to understand?
Oh, my...
Now get the hell out of my house.
Wait.
Are you going to be okay?
Thank you.
Good luck.
Just after 7:00 AM, March 22nd,
the Annual Purge
has just concluded.
This is your American
morning news program.
And reports are coming in
from all around the country
as police, firefighters
and paramedics...
The New Founding Fathers
have released an early statement saying
this was the most
successful Purge yet.
I am walking...
I should say "stumbling"
through downtown Los Angeles,
and there are literally
bodies everywhere.
I witnessed
a group of young men
breaking into
the tenement next to me,
and they were
dragging people out
and just executing
them on the street.
Hundreds have gathered in
Times Square
for a public vigil
thanking all those
who were killed last night
for their sacrifice to make
this country a safer place.
They are turning people away
from emergency rooms
in Brownsville
as there is simply
no more room.
The markets were up this morning
as both gun and
home security system
quarterly sales
reports were released
announcing profits
in both sectors.
We have 364
long days until the next Purge.
So let's get all our Purge
talk and analysis in today
while our thoughts
are still fresh.
From what I've been reading, it seems
like Dallas had the most participants.
I did get a chance to see some
live surveillance footage
out of Dallas, Forest Lawn,
and there had to be 200
people in the town square
purging at the same time.
Never saw anything like this.
I lost my two sons last night.
My boys.
Yeah, I was a proud American.
Not anymore.
This country has taken
everything from me.